Praise God, praise God,
God is faithful. I say God
is faithful. How many of you
believe that? Before you sit
down, I want you to rejoice.
Rejoice!
Hallelujah! Amen!
Praise God. Sit down. Sacred
Assembly is a rejoicing church.
Joy is our attitude. You know,
Paul writing to Timothy said
that I'm writing this so that
you will know how ye ought to
behave. In this place, our
behavior is joy. Joy is
our behavior. Oh, we behave
joy! We behave joy!
Amazing testimonies, and the
testimonies we had this morning
is just a fraction of what God
has done. We have about 5
7-figure income just in the
month of August alone. Well,
you may think it is nothing,
but, uh, You had,
you had the testimony, what
they've been believing God for
since 2023. See, there's
something about you stepping
into the season that God has
marked for harvest.
And you know what God is saying
to us? He's saying that, well,
all the sheaves you brought in,
in the month of August, is
subject to your capacity. And
that is why he's saying that in
September stretch. So we are
still bringing in the sheaves
this month, but we are
stretching. I said we are
stretching. Hallelujah!
Praise God! You know, the Lord
say I should tell you that
before the end of this year is
giving people land and
properties.
Yeah, I see God
giving people land and
properties. And then I see
building properties.
Some of you, you are making the
down payment before the end of
this year. You are making the
down payment. Some of you
listening to me, you will live
in the house you did not build.
Ownership without purchase,
ridiculously subsidized
ownership. In the name of Jesus.
Thank you, Father. My wife
preached a storm last week,
isn't it?
Amen. So, so I, I think it,
it is time I can now move on.
Amen. Praise God forevermore.
I want us to open our Bibles to
the book of Luke chapter 15.
How many of you were blessed by
my wife's message last week?
Someone was telling me, say,
Papa, you need to listen to that
message so you'll be blessed.
Amen. Luke chapter 15. I was in
Abuja church last week Sunday,
and what God is doing in their
midst is amazing. You guys
better fasten your seat belts.
I was, I was envious of the
things that God is doing in the
city of Abuja, and I felt I
should just move to Abuja for a
while. Luke chapter 15,
I'm going to read from verse 3.
And so he told them this
parable, saying, what man among
you, if he has 100 sheep
and has lost one of them, does
not leave the other 99 in the
open pasture and go after the
one that is lost until he finds
it? And when he has found it,
he puts it on his shoulders,
rejoicing. And when he comes
home, he calls together his
friends and neighbors, saying to
them, 'Rejoice with me, because
I have found my sheep that was
lost!' I tell you that in the
same way there will be more joy
in heaven over one sinner who
repents than over 99 righteous
people who have no need of
repentance. Praise God!
September is our month of soul
winning, and all my teachings
through this month, both the
Yearning of Faith and, uh,
Sunday services, will be
centered around soul winning.
Soul winning is one of the areas
that God will have us to stretch
this month. We have the
instruction to stretch in the
place of prayer. This week we
are going to be embarking on
fasting and praying, and we are
also going to be having prayer
chain. And we also, uh, told to
stretch in our giving, uh, this
month. Praise God! God has
commanded you to sustain
something in the house. You may
not know, but I will help you
like Elijah helped the woman.
And the third instruction on
stretching is in soul winning.
Soul winning. And of all the
areas that God will have us to
stretch this month, soul winning
is that one that has eternal
bearing. Now, when I'm preaching
on joy on salvation, I'm not,
I'm not just talking about the
joy that you experience when
you got born again. Of course,
it is going to be part of what
I'll be talking about here. But
one thing I want you to
understand about joy and
salvation is that they are
almost inseparable in scripture.
Everywhere salvation is
mentioned, whether the promise
of salvation or the experience
of salvation in Scripture, it is
always accompanied by joy.
In fact, the joy of salvation is
not just an individual or
personal experience of the one
who is the recipient of
salvation. Bible says that there
is also joy in heaven over one
sinner that gets born again. So
when you talk or sing about,
you know, making God happy,
giving God joy, it is not just
in your lifestyle, all right?
The ultimate way your life can
bring joy to heaven is soul
winning. Are you getting what
I'm saying here? Oh, do you
understand what I'm saying? So
joy is not— joy is
not just, uh, you know, it's not
just something that springs from
salvation. It is with joy,
Isaiah 12:3, it is with joy that
we draw waters from the wells of
salvation. In the book of Acts,
Bible says that there was joy,
there was joy in the city.
Acts chapter 9, Bible says that
when Philip went to Samaria to
preach the gospel, Bible said
that there was joy in the city.
You cannot separate salvation
from joy. And this is very
important because many of us,
we have lost the joy of
salvation. It's very possible
for you to lose the joy of
salvation. Losing the joy of
salvation simply means that the
knowledge of salvation or your
experience of salvation is no
longer producing springs of joy.
And this happens for different
reasons. The reason some people
have lost their joy of salvation
is because they are not well
taught on the subject of
salvation. In fact, one of the
major reasons many Christians do
not experience the joy of
salvation is because they lack
the assurance of salvation. If
my salvation is per good
thing that I do. If my salvation
is subject to my efforts, then
it means that the, the salvation
is more of a burden than a
delight. There are some people
that salvation is the source of
their greatest anxiety because
they don't know whether if Jesus
comes today, they are going.
How many of you believe that if
Jesus come right now as I'm
speaking, you are going? Let me
see your hand. I like sincere
people. You know, it's going to
be sincere so that I know how to
help you. Okay, it's not going
to be making assumption. All
right, if you are— and I don't
form— don't, don't form. If you
believe, or if you know that if
Jesus comes right now as I'm
speaking, you are going with
Jesus, let me see your hand up.
Now you see, the reason,
the reason some people are not
too certain about it is because
they,
they don't just know.
And maybe that is one of the
reasons why you are not
experiencing the joy of
salvation. Praise God.
But the thing is this, if you
are born again— okay, how many
of you are born again in this
place? Let me see your hand.
Hurray! Now what? Okay, no, let
me see your hand. If you are
born again, let me see your
hand. You're born again. Now you
see, if I asked, if I
asked you if you are born again
And I asked if you are going to
be with Jesus if he comes. It is
the same question. What prepares
you for rapture is salvation.
There is nothing more. You, you
can't improve. See, salvation is
the complete preparation of God
for your rapture.
Whatever happens between your
salvation and rapture is
completely inconsequential on
your rapture ability. Permit me
to use that word. Are you
getting what I'm saying here?
So God prepares us in salvation
for rapture. Bible says that
salvation is the down payment
that God has made for us,
and Holy Spirit is the seal of
that salvation. Are you
following what I'm saying here?
So I understand that there are
people that are not even sure
whether they are born again,
but the thing is this: if you
have ever heard the gospel, you
heard about the gospel of the
death, burial, and the
resurrection of Jesus, and the
implications of these three
events, that you believe that
Jesus died for your sin and he
was raised for your
justification, and you believe
it with your heart, you are born
again. And the moment you
believe that, you are
raptureable.
If your raptureability depends
on your efforts, that means your
effort is your savior, not
Jesus. So it means the
blood of Jesus is not perfect
for your redemption. If any man
could save himself, Jesus will
not need to come. So the reason
many people have lost the joy of
their salvation is because of
lack of assurance, lack of
certainty about their salvation.
Salvation is not pay-as-you-go.
Salvation is not in installment.
Salvation is a complete reality.
Your sins are forgiven. Your
past, your present, and your
future sins are forgiven. And
some people will argue, yes, I
agree that my past sins are
forgiven. I know that the sin
I'm committing right now, if I
ask God for forgiveness, he will
forgive me. But why will you say
that my future sins are
forgiven? When Jesus died, your
sin today, where was it? Was it
in the past, present, or future?
Of Jesus when he died. It was in
So the reason people lack the
joy of salvation is uncertainty,
lack of assurance,
lack of assurance.
But you see, the joy of
salvation is an eternal joy
because salvation that produces
this joy is eternal.
It is eternal. Another reason
people don't experience the joy
of salvation is guilt and
condemnation. That's why in
Isaiah— sorry, Psalm 51, Paul—
sorry, David, I think verse 12,
it says, restore unto me the joy
of salvation. So what happened
is that when you sin Guilt
and condemnation robs you of the
joy of salvation. But do you
know what we have in the New
Testament? Paul says in Romans
chapter 8, verse 1, it says,
now therefore there is no
condemnation for those who are
in Christ Jesus. It means that
even when you sin, he said,
know that you have an advocate
with the Father. So you must
never allow condemnation or
guilt of sin to rob you of— see,
some of you here, you are OG,
you will agree with me that you
feel guilty about something does
not mean you will not return to
it. See, guilt is that trap that
devil consistently use to lure
people back to what they are
sorry for.
God knows you will never be able
to break away from that habit,
you will never be able to break
away from that thing that is
causing guilt and condemnation.
And that is the reason he did
not just take your sin away, he
also fixed condemnation.
And the way God fixed
condemnation is through
righteousness. See, God's
solution to sin is not
sinlessness, it is
righteousness. You will never be
able to attain sinlessness as
long as you are here on earth.
That is the reason for rapture,
so that this mortal body will
take up immortal, so that this
corruptible shall take Wake up
incorruptible. It was
Ayobabalola that was on the
mountain one day praying, and
he's been there for days, for
weeks. You know when you are
just alone with God and you feel
so clean? And he asked God, he
said, God— he read the scripture
that if God wants to mark sin,
no one shall stand. He now asked
God, he said, God, I've been
here alone fellowshipping with
your spirit Have I committed
anything? Is there any sin you
have to forgive?
And God told him, he said, you
commit nothing less than 200
sins per second, even right
here with me.
If God wants to mark sin, who
shall stand? But forgiveness is
with thee, so that man will fear
thee. The source of the fear of
God is forgiveness, not threat
Man's logic thinks that if we
can threaten people with hell,
they will live right. He said,
but forgiveness is with thee.
He said, this forgiveness, this
knowledge of forgiveness is what
inspires reference, referential
fear. In the heart of man.
So God's answer is
righteousness, and this
righteousness is a position that
God has brought you into,
that no matter what has
happened, you can stand before
God without fear,
without inferiority complex.
That is righteousness.
So the reason many Christians
have lost the joy of their
salvation is the scourge of
guilt and condemnation.
There's no condemnation for
those who are in Christ Jesus.
There's no condemnation. Say,
there's no condemnation for me.
Louder, say, there's no
condemnation. Bible says that he
that believes, he that believes
shall be saved. He said the one
who believe not is condemned
already. So salvation brought
you out of condemnation.
So Pastor, it means that even if
I do anything wrong, I should
not feel bad? No, I'm not
talking about remorse. There's a
difference between remorse and
condemnation.
And what condemnation does is
that it drives you away from God
in your consciousness.
Any salvation that you receive
that is not eternal is made in
China. The salvation
that Jesus gives is eternal.
Even the makeshift atonement
procured by the blood of goats
lasts for one year.
The, the atonement procured by
the blood of goats, animals,
will last an entire nation for
one year. But you, you thought
that yours is per
second or per minute. If the
blood of goats can atone for a
nation for one year, how much
more the blood of Jesus?
Bible says that he offered his
blood as an eternal sacrifice.
Once and for all, and then he
sits. He sits because the work
is done. Now John says that if
you sin, know that you have an
advocate with the Father.
Say, know that you have an
So guilt and condemnation robs
people of the joy of their
salvation. And that is why you
must know that it doesn't matter
the mistakes that you make.
Never forget that God loves you
still. It doesn't matter
what has happened to you. It
doesn't matter what you have
failed at. Know that God loves
you still.
Is that very clear? Say, God
loves me. I am his son. If when
I was a sinner, when I was dead
in sin, he died for me because
he loved me, how much more now
that I am alive unto him?
He said he has uphold me with
the right hand of his
righteousness. That is why Jesus
said that no man can pluck them
away from me. He's upholding us
with the right hand of his own,
his own righteousness.
You put so much, so much weight
on your own efforts, and that's
why you are limited in life.
Those who reign in life, they
reign through the scepter of
righteousness. Said those who
have received these gifts of
righteousness, they shall reign
on heads.
This righteousness, it is not
just what makes us to be at
peace with God. This
righteousness is our scepter of
dominion,
that it doesn't matter what
happens, God is for me. God is
not against me. God is for me.
Bible says Abraham believed God,
it was counted unto him for
righteousness. Even when Abraham
sinned, when he lied, because of
this righteousness that has been
credited to his account, God
could not lay any charge against
him. Rather, God went to meet
the innocent king. Why did you
take the wife of this prophet?
Yahweh restore his wife.
Are you getting what I'm saying
here? Another reason some people
have lost the joy of their
salvation is because they fell,
they took the bait of the enemy.
They begin to look at the
ephemeral things of this world
for joy, and devil quietly
substituted the joy of
salvation with the happiness of
accomplishments. But you see,
happiness is always— happiness
is like drug. You can never take
enough. You can never take
enough. Some of you here, God
gave you a miracle in the month
of August. Now you had people
coming and sharing testimony. I
got a job in 7 figures. What is
this ₦150,000 job that I'm
happy? Is this, is this what my
mates are receiving? Nothing is
small until it is compared.
Comparison is the reason many of
you have lost the joy of
salvation. And devil is very
smart. He will start by first
giving you things to be happy
about. Until he has completely
disconnected you from the joy of
salvation, disconnected your joy
from salvation to the things of
life. So your joy is roller
coaster, it is on and off, more
epileptic than Nepalites.
Some of you, you say that I
don't know what is happening,
it's as if— now I see, doctors
will have explanation They say
you are having personality
disorder, you are bipolar. No,
your, your problem is that you
are not satisfied with the joy
that comes from salvation.
Is as if there are just some
people that God is just blessing
in this church. How about me?
Share the testimony of the
One of them that shared
testimony, I asked him, I said,
how much is your salary? He told
me. I said, I thought you are
earning a 7-figure, so this is
the amount? No, no, don't worry,
you have to earn. You, you just
have to earn a 7-figure. It was
the month after they got the
job. First, be okay where you
are. Never take the bait. Even
when things are going good in
your life, never, never, never
uproot your joy, from salvation
to the good things going on in
your life. Don't let the devil
pull the rug under you. It's a
trap. Put premium
on your salvation.
I don't like where I'm living.
I don't like where I'm— see,
where you are, you can beautify
it. That one-room apartment you
are staying, go and get a used
AC, put it there.
Say no, it is until when I move
to a bigger— that bigger place
will not come if you don't
enjoy, because joy is how you
make progress. It is a
triumphant procession. It's a
triumphant procession. You can't
proceed without joy.
Go and paint that one-room
apartment, decorate it, buy the
fake art they are selling along
Lekki Expressway, put it there.
If you can't afford a new AC,
buy a used one, put it there.
Are you getting what I'm saying?
If you want to do, get ready
with me. As long as you are not
showing your nakedness, do it.
Let people be able to track the
progress. Bible says that, and
the heathen saw and they said,
'Kai, God has done great things
for them.' The heathen knew
where they were before.
All the things doctors are
telling you about your mental
health, I'm giving you divine
diagnosis. It is because you
lack the joy of salvation.
Salvation is a joke to you that
God had to become man and die
for you. Went to your place in
hell, took your place. And guess
what? Where or what he delivered
you from is the least of the
good news. It is the life he has
brought you into.
Somebody sang, if I can turn
back the hand of time, I will go
back to the Garden of Eden. Not
me and you, Garden of Eden. He
has brought us into eternal
Now hear me, eternal life was
not a response to Adam's sin.
Eternal life has been the
original plan of God from the
beginning. So whether Adam ate
the fruit or not, he will still
need eternal life. Uh-uh.
You want to go back to Garden of
Eden to be eating apple,
avocado?
Hey, he has given eternal life.
He that has the Son has eternal
life. So I have come that you
will have this life abundantly.
That is what you have in
salvation. The ultimate gift of
salvation is not just
forgiveness of sin, it's not
just justification. It is
eternal life, God kind of life.
There is
a reason a man can only bark
like dog.
He will learn how to bark like
dog, but a dog barks
effortlessly. Why? It is the
function of the life in it.
Say, I have eternal life.
These are the things that God by
Spirit revealed to Paul that
gave him the audacity to tell
you to rejoice forevermore. He
cannot say you should rejoice
forevermore because of car. You
are rejoicing because of iPhone.
This September, I think they
will release iPhone 17 or 18.
So the one that you had, that
you are thinking you're on top
of the world, is out of vogue.
How can that joy be eternal?
I'm trusting God for SUV 2026
special edition,
except the sun will not go down,
except time will stop. Once you
cross into the following year,
your car become old model. In
fact, the moment you drive it
out of the dealer shop, it
become secondhand. How can that
thing now give you eternal joy?
The joy of salvation. You have
a lot to learn from David.
Bible said David never lost a
battle in his life, never lost a
battle. Yet when he realized
that he's out of tune with God,
he cried. He said, ah, restore
to me the joy, because his
strength to win in battle— the
joy of the Lord is your
strength. He knows that once
Once this joy is drained out of
his soul, he will become
vulnerable to the enemy.
It is joy. This joy,
this joy, salvation. This joy,
salvation.
Never let life accomplishments—
give thanks to God for whatever
he has done, no, for no victory
is small. People talk about
small mercy. There's no mercy
that is small. Give thanks,
rejoice for that, but let your
joy be anchored on your
salvation, that you have eternal
life, that you are, you are,
you are one with God, that God
is for you and not against you,
that God is not angry with you,
that your voice is the voice he
wants to hear first thing in the
morning, that God delights in
your prosperity.
Praise God. There's something
amazing. I, I, I, I— is it Luke
10? When the disciples came to
Jesus to talk about the
exploits, their success in
ministry. God was the one that
gave them the assignment and
they succeeded at it and they
were happy and they came to
Jesus. 'Oh Jesus, we have
succeeded, we have exploit.' He
said, 'Don't rejoice in those
things.' He
said, 'In this you should
rejoice, that your name is
written.' Your name is written.
Jesus is saying that even
ministry exploits can never
match the joy of salvation.
If ministry exploits is nothing
to compare, how come it is not
your career accomplishment?
Because they refuse to promote
you after 3 years. That's the
reason you are sad.
Abakusida said, even if the fig
tree does not bear, even if
there is no— no, the earth does
not yield, the land does not
yield, nothing happen, he said,
I will joy in the God of
my salvation.
Because every provision God has
made in salvation, it is through
joy you will fetch it out.
Many people worry too much about
devourer. You don't understand
this life. He said the enemy
came to steal, kill, and
destroy, but I have come to give
eternal life. He didn't say that
I have come to restore what the
enemy took. He said I've come to
give eternal life. A man called
MKO had a glimpse of the
understanding of this thing.
They asked him that, are you not
scared of losing your wealth to
the devourer? He said, I don't
care about the devourer. He
said, if the devourer should
come to my finance, he said,
the devourer will eat, eat,
eat, and die. Mindset.
Jesus did not say that I'm going
to restore what is stolen. He
said, I've come to give eternal
life. I've come to give eternal
life. It is a replenishing life.
And they stole your phone, you
are fasting and praying,
Father, touch the heart of that
person, let the person restore
my phone. Uh, God will not touch
the heart of the person.
Settle it.
There are some prayers I don't
waste my time to pray.
One Wednesday like that, we're
done with meeting, and
downstairs a couple went
to get something. So I was there
waiting for them, waiting with
their kids. Before they are
back, my phone had become a view
once, you know, view once. I
couldn't see it again. As I was
about to enter the car, my wife
said, where's your phone?
I knew that it's gone
immediately. I just took it off
my mind. He says that I did not
come to return what the enemy
stole. I came to give eternal
life and to have it more
abundantly. This life will
replenish whatever is depleted
in your life. You will not even
know that anything leave your
For everyone that has lost
anything, hear the word of the
Lord: it will be replenished.
God does not do refund. What God
does is restoration. Even under
the law, restoration is not the
same thing you lost. It always
come with interest.
Yes, you lost a job, better one
Better one is what? Is coming.
The brother shared testimony
when he told me about what they
are doing. They want to, uh,
they've cut off the salary. I
know, I say, yes, see, you will
reap in another field. Some of
you, your time is up in that
company, but yeah, with
everything I have done, uh, you
don't reap where you sow, you
only you reap what
you sow, the field will be
different.
That's what has kept some people
in a very toxic relationship.
Ah, I have suffered with him,
I've suffered.
Ah, the fruit of long suffering
is meant for the gospel.
Not for toxic relationship.
That if this gospel will cost
you to suffer, you have the
ability to endure.
It may only be useful if you
make a bad choice and then you
are in that relationship, it
will help you. But you are still
dating, I've suffered with him,
I remember when I gave him my
entire salary. Ah, don't worry,
God has a compensation for you.
Sela. Praise God. Amen.
Glory to God forevermore.
You must learn how to keep your
joy. You must learn how to
increase in joy.
Don't despise this salvation
that you have. This salvation is
so big. Bible says that what,
how, what, what will happen to
us if we are to escape this
great salvation? This salvation
is called great salvation.
Let the light, let the eyes of
your understanding be
enlightened. In the name of
Jesus, that you will know the
hope of your calling. In the
name of Jesus, let the light—
eyes of your understanding, let
it be enlightened. Let it be
enlightened in the name of
Jesus. Praise God forevermore.
Oh, thank you, Lord Jesus.
Never let any material things or
life accomplishment to replace
the source of your joy.
Is that clear? Keep your joy,
the joy of your salvation. That
is the joy that will replenish
whatever it is you have lost.
Habakkuk said that I will
rejoice in the God of my
salvation. And the next thing he
said that he will make my feet
like hinds' feet and he will
cause me to walk upon my high in
the time of famine. He said,
because I have kept my joy in
the God of my salvation, he will
make my feet like hind's feet.
A translation says that he will
give me the feet of a mountain
goat. This mountain goat, they
are experts, experts in climbing
rocks. You would think they will
fall if you watch Najuwa. You
would think they will trip and
fall. No, you see them gliding
gracefully in dangerous terrain.
It is by the joy of salvation.
Praise God.
I just kept my mind on what
Jesus told the disciples. You
see, pastors are committing
suicide. There are many pastors
that are just showing up. They
are no longer there. They are
discouraged. Jesus said
that, see, don't let your joy be
anchored on the exploits. That
it means that even when what you
are doing is not working, the
fact that your name is in the
Book of Life, it is the greatest
So you must learn how to keep
your joy. You must learn how to
keep this joy bubbling, how to
keep this joy flowing. And the
number one reason is that you
feed on the word of God.
Feed on the gospel.
Paul says in Colossians 3:16,
it says, let the word of Christ
dwell in you richly.
Feed richly on the gospel.
The word of Christ, logos of
Christ, is talking about the
wisdom of God revealed in Christ
Jesus, and that is what we call
the gospel. I love what Jeremiah
said. He said that your word
have I found and I did eat them,
and it is the joy and the
rejoicing of my heart. Your word
have I found, and I did eat
them. Your word have I found,
and I did eat them. It is the
joy and the rejoicing of my
heart. What keeps
your joy bubbling? What keeps
your joy flowing is you feeding
on God's word.
Feed on the gospel. You know,
many of you, you don't see the
correlation between what you are
currently— how you are currently
feeling and the gospel. I was
listening to a brother's
testimony in Abuja, and he said
something that is very, very,
you know, something that really
struck a chord in me. He said it
was just nothing was working
around him. And he was just
feeling sad, depressed. Nothing
was working. And he went to meet
his friend. You need to have
right people in your life. He
says he was talking to the
person, he said, that's when he
just told him, I said, see, I am
diagnosing you right now. What I
see you lack, your issue is
gospel deficiency. You need to
feed on the gospel. Some of you,
you are going through gospel
deficiency. It is only
reflecting in your mood, in your
emotion, in the things around
around you. What is deficient in
your life is the gospel.
Are you following what I'm
Feed on the gospel. Never take
the gospel for the ground. See,
he talks, they say, this is the
gospel that I preach unto you.
1 Corinthians chapter 15, he
said, this is the gospel that I
have preached unto you. Which
you have received and wherein
you stand. Some people think
that gospel is just for the
kindergartens. If you want to
come into the gospel, into the
kingdom, I want you to even
listen to pastors who say stuff
like, you see, all those things
they are talking about, the
gospel is for kindergartens.
After you come in, you now move
on to see even the mature things
we are moving on to is the
gospel. We are only more
skillful in the word of
righteousness, not in the word
of the work of our effort.
In the word of righteousness.
Praise God. Tell them, say,
feed on the word of God.
Feed on the word of God. Number
2, share the joy of salvation
through the gospel.
Share what? The joy of
salvation. Through the gospel.
Bible says in the text, Luke
chapter 15, from verse 3,
verse 7 says, there is joy in
heaven for one sinner that
repents. There is joy in heaven
Joy in heaven for one sinner
that repents. Everywhere Bible
talks about people receiving the
gospel in scripture, their
response is with joy. In
Samaria, Bible said there was
joy in the city.
The Enoch was rejoicing as he
was going. The jailers,
after the miracle, the
earthquake miracle, Bible says
that they cry out to Paul 'What
shall we do to be saved?' After
they believed the gospel and
were baptized, the Bible said
that they went on rejoicing.
Be the reason somebody will
experience this joy of
salvation. Share the joy of
salvation through the gospel.
And that is to tell you that
preaching the gospel is not
something you do out of, you
know, religious— a sense of
religious duty. You do it with
excitement. The way your
countenance is the reason people
don't like to listen to you,
because you look like somebody
that has come with bad news.
Jesus saves, he has forgiven.
You are not, you don't. There's
a story, true life story of an
American preacher, American
priest, is one of those that
they call to, you know,
administer the final rites to
criminals that are going to be
executed. So before these people
were going to be hanged, they
called this man of God to preach
the gospel to them. You know,
he's been doing it for long.
There was no excitement, no
emotion, nothing. He just
preached the gospel to the man,
and after he was done, the man
asked him, he said, please,
what you are telling me, is it
true? He said, yes, it is true.
He said, I don't believe it.
Because if this thing you are
talking about is true, and now
where you— I am going to crawl
on broken bottles, I will cross
7 seas, climb 7 mountains to
share the gospel with just one
person. You mean this good news
is something you are just
sharing with plain face like it
Bible says this salvation gives
joy. You can't be sharing it
with a frown face or a plain
sharing the Gospel.
Have you seen GNLG and New Life
people before with
shoes that have given them
artificial bow leg, and yet they
are so excited? My brother, I
want to share something good
with you. In fact, it will
change you. We were somewhere
one day, and one came to us You
know, unconsciously I just look
at the feet, the shoe and all
that. God bless you.
There was even one I had to
transfer body to.
Just use this one to take him
Now those are the people that
are doing new life, oh. But you,
you are doing eternal life. You
should be more excited.
You should be more excited. I'm
a dealer in eternal life.
I deal in eternal life. He said
the first man was a living soul.
He said the last man is a
life-giving spirit. You are a
life-giving spirit in Christ.
It means that when you preach
this gospel, you are imparting
eternal life.
Is that very clear? Share the
gospel. You know what Jesus said
in John chapter 4, uh, I think
verse 35, thereabout? It says
that so that he that sow and
he that reap shall rejoice
together. That is the way you
keep this joy bubbling.
And if you are a soul winner,
you will know this joy I'm
talking about. That's not just
the person receiving the gospel
that is rejoicing. Even you that
preach the gospel, you are
Even though my wife has been
preaching this gospel for years,
even last on Saturday, she went
to make her hair and got
somebody born again. You see
that childlike excitement.
This thing gives you joy,
and this joy is greater than any
joy that any dollar can give
you. You don't know it because
of your value system.
Is that very clear? And the
third thing I will share with
you before I go: never allow
material things— I've said it
before, but I'm highlighting it
again— Never let material
things, never let any earthly
things to replace the salvation
as the source of your joy.
Is that clear? Never allow
anything to replace
salvation as the source of your
joy.
Praise God.
Never let anything to replace
salvation as the source of your
joy. Thank God for promotion,
thank God for lifting, thank God
for new opportunities, but never
anchor any of these things—
never anchor your joy rather on
any of these things. Praise God.
So you set your heart on— you
set your affection on things
above. Colossians chapter 3.
Colossians chapter 3. Put out
that scripture quickly. Verse,
verse 1.
Praise God.
Bible says that we set our
affection. If then be risen— if
ye then be risen with Christ,
seek those things which are
above. Where Christ sits on the
right hand of God. Move on. Set
your affection on things above,
not on things on the earth. Set
not on things on the earth.
That is how to keep your joy.
Let your obsession be on eternal
verities, not on earthly
accomplishments. Are you getting
what I'm saying here? I've seen
people who have come to
genuinely lament, complain to me
about what they are going
through in the same job they
came to share testimony about.
That is to tell you that there
is nothing you are celebrating
today. Oh, you got a new car.
That is not really new, but for
you it is new. By the time you
start changing, you start
changing brake pads, you start
changing crankshaft, you want to
question God. God, is it not
even good that you live?
Praise God. I remember one time
our car engine knocked, so we
had to be taking boat, and I
told my wife, is this not the
better life? Ah, like he will
just come pick us, we'll just
pay. A fraction of what would
have used to fèka. That is to
tell you that, see, there is
nothing material that can give
you enduring joy. That husband
you are thanking God for now,
the wife you are thanking God
for now, say you don't used to
fight. People will now see you
with all your, your pancake,
they will think that you are
better people.
Praise God. You know that you
used to fight.
Praise God!
A woman of God said something.
He said, see, if you see me
whispering to my husband in the
course of service, don't think
we are discussing the
advancement of the ministry. We
continue the fight from home.
You that have been with me for a
long time understand this.
Service can be going and I will
call you. And I will whisper
something to your ear, and
everybody will, you know, they
will be shaking their head. You
would think that I'm giving them
prophecy. You don't want to hear
what I'm saying.
I won't be tempted to say what I
used to say. I'm a changed man.
I don't do that anymore. One day
I told a brother in the car, I
said, call the brother for me.
Everybody was rejoicing and I
just whispered something. He
said, okay, sir. All right,
sir.
Don't let me tell you what I
said. So that is to tell that,
see, things are not just the way
it is. You see young folks, how
you can't wait to marry so you
can just be having sex. Uh, you
better have more serious reason
One of my friend's mom said that
thing to us, to my friend
actually. He got somebody
pregnant, we were in SS2, and
the mother said something that
stayed with me. Say, ah,
benga, ah,
something that you will eat,
eat, eat, you will be tired of
Like you will be— you almost
want to— you, it will be so—
you'll be so full that you will
see it, you'll not be
interested. I mean, let this
salvation be your joy.
So the car you share testimony
about, you're almost questioning
God about the same car.
I, I asked one of my sons, you
didn't bring your car to Papa?
We just pack it up.
Ah, be contented with the
joy of salvation. Let this
salvation mean something to you.
Is that very clear? And the last
thing— rise on your feet— be
intentional about the practice
of joy,
because this joy of salvation is
not a feeling. Yes, sir.
You did not get born again
because you feel like. You made
a choice. Same way, the joy of
salvation is more than a
feeling. It is a decision.
Habakkuk says that even if the
field does not produce, even if
there is no fig on the tree,
even if there is nothing in the
barn, he said, I will rejoice in
the God of my salvation. I will
rejoice. It is a choice. This
joy is not circumstance-based.
This joy is salvation-based. I
will rejoice in the God of
salvation. It is a choice. Is
that very clear? It is a choice.
Because you are seated— the
Bible says he that sits in
heaven shall what? Shall laugh.
It is a choice. Are you seated
with Christ in the heavenly
places, far above
principalities? No, I don't
know. The way you show it is by
rejoicing. Can you rejoice
in the Holy Ghost? Rejoice in
the Holy Ghost! He that sits
in heaven shall laugh. He that
sits in heaven shall laugh.
I think we should have a joy
service this month where we just
come here to laugh at the enemy.
Say, why are the head erased?
How? Why did the kings gather in
conspiracy against his anointed?
He that sits in heaven shall
laugh. He shall have them in
jealousy.
See, that joy is what caused
confusion in the camp of the
enemy. With everything they are
doing, they expect certain
reaction. Now seeing you
laughing, seeing you rejoicing,
you are confused. Can you laugh
in the Holy Ghost?
Rejoice in the Lord!
Look at your account, look at
the dashboard of your bank app
and laugh.
Landlord has come with a quit
notice— laugh! Hear me,
In this kingdom, we don't have
the last laugh. We have the
first, the second, the middle,
and the last laugh. Tell your
neighbor, say, in this kingdom,
we don't just have the last
laugh. Say, we have the first.
Say, we have the half laugh,
and we have the middle laugh,
and we have the omega laugh.
I'm not going to laugh last too.
I will laugh first.
You didn't get it? I will laugh
first and I will still laugh
last. While you are conspiring
against me, I will respond with
laughter. They say
you're time is up, just laugh.
They threaten you that we will
show you, we will make sure that
you will not be established.
Just laugh at them.
He that sits in heaven
laughs.
The only time anybody laughed in
heaven was out of ignorance.
John says that who shall open